

Andre Madarang Full Stack Web Developer

% andremadarang.com

□ andre.madarang@gmail.com

My primary interest is in web development, both front end and back end. The industry is fast paced and constantly moving forward. It is one that requires constant education throughout your entire career. This is exciting to me as there will always be new things to learn and new challenges to overcome. I primarily specialize on the LEMP (PHP) stack, with emphasis on the Laravel PHP framework and the ecosystem that surrounds it.

Experience

andremadarang.com

Jan 2013 - Present

Freelance Web Developer / Designer

I design and develop websites and web applications to meet the business requirements of my clients. Every client is different so my work ranges from basic static websites to more complex web applications. Have a look at my online portfolio/website for examples of client work, code samples and testimonials.

Blast Radius

Jun 2016 - Jun 2017

Front End Developer

Worked on several projects ranging from WordPress sites, .NET, and Laravel stacks. Responsibilities included implementing new features, fixing existing bugs, co-ordinating with other developers and project managers, improving code quality, improving technology stacks and delvering the needs of our clients.

OISE | Continuing and Professional Learning University of Toronto

May 2009 - Jan 2015

Coordinator of On-line Initiatives

Responsible for setting up, maintaining and proving support for several online courses using "Blackboard" Learning Management system. I was also responsible for maintaining and updating several websites and their respective databases. Furthermore, I automated repetitive tasks to make things easier to accomplish (i.e. online registration site, online waiting lists for students, etc.).

Education

Honours Bachelor of Science in Computer Science University of Toronto

2002 - 2008

Specialist: Software Engineering

Skills

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript/JQuery Git / Version Control
- PHP/MySQL
- VueJS

• Servers / Deployment

- Laravel
- WordPress
- UI/UX Design

I also enjoy teaching Web Development topics on YouTube. Be sure to check out my screencasts which will give you a good idea of the technologies I'm into.

https://www.youtube.com/drehimself

Interests















